Pribram, Karl; Papers ger005
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications of Karl Pribram, 1904-1951; 6; 192 file folders
  - Reviews, 1902-1958; 6.11
    - Crosser, Paul K. Economic Fictions -- A Critique of Subjectivistic Economic Theory, ca. 1958 (Box 11 (6-Publications of Karl Pribram), Folder 25)
- Publications by others, Undated; 7; 8 file folders
  This series contains primarily reprints of articles sent to Pribram by other scholars.
  - Amonn, Alfred, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 26)
  - Appleman, Adolph, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 27)
  - Aufricht, Hans, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 28)
  - Bab, Herbert, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 29)
  - Blachly, Dan, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 30)
  - Böhm-Bawerk, Eugen v., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 31)
  - Chaudhury, Nagendra Nath, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 32)
  - Fisher, Irving, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 33)
  - Forchheimer, Karl, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 34)
  - Freudenberger, Herman, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 35)
  - Froehlich, Walter, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 36)
  - Goetz, B. E., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 37)
  - Grebler, Leo, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 38)
  - Grunberg, Emile, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 39)
  - Haber, William / Joseph, J. J., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 40)
  - Heimann, Eduard, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 41)
  - Hesselbach, Walter, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 42)
  - Hexner, Ervin, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 43)
  - Letiche, John M., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 44)
  - Mannheim, Karl, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 45)
  - Mises, Ludwig von, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 46)
  - Mitchell, Wesley C., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 47)
  - Neumark, F., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 48)
  - Nyström, Bertil, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 49)
  - Pribram, Ewald, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 50)
  - Pribram, Karl H., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 51)
  - Rice, Stuart, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 52)
  - Richter-Altschaeffer, Hans, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 53)
  - Schiff, Eric, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 54)
  - Schlochauer, H. J., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 55)
  - Schoenbaum, Emil, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 56)
  - Schultz, Henry, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 57)
  - Schumpeter, Joseph, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 58)
  - Sebba, Gregor, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 59)
  - Spielmans, John V., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 60)
  - Spitzer, H. M., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 61)
  - Sulzbach, Walter, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 62)
  - Vito, Francesco, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 63)
  - Weddigen, Walter, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 64)
  - Weisskopf, Walter A., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 65)
  - White, Leonard D., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 66)
  - Wieser, Friedrich Freiherrn v., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 67)
  - Witte, Edwin E., Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 68)
  - Wunderlich, Frieda, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 69)
  - Zaglits, Oscar, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 70)
  - Zahn, Friedrich, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 71)
  - Miscellaneous publications, Undated (Box 11 (7-Publications by others), Folder 72)